{
  "title": "Expressions with death, marriage and divorce",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Her father's ......... came as great shock to all those who knew him. ",
      "answers": ["dead", "died", "death", "die"],
      "correct": "death"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Did you hear? James and Beth ........ last week. ",
      "answers": ["get married", "been married", "got married", "married"],
      "correct": "got married"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Our poor old dog is ......... We've had him for fourteen years. He just sleeps all day long. ",
      "answers": ["dead", "dying", "death", "die"],
      "correct": "dying"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "The young girl screamed when she saw the ........ body sprawled out on her living room floor. ",
      "answers": ["dead", "dying", "death", "die"],
      "correct": "dead"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "We had a lovely ........ in a small country church. The ceremony was presided over by our parish priest. ",
      "answers": ["reception", "marriage", "wedding", "honeymoon"],
      "correct": "wedding"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "My great grandfather's body was lost at sea in a horrific boat accident yesterday. A ....... will be held for him at the Presbyterian church next Thursday. ",
      "answers": ["funeral", "burial", "cremation", "memorial service"],
      "correct": "memorial service"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Helen is planning to ........ with Michael. ",
      "answers": ["marry", "elope", "engage", "divorce"],
      "correct": "elope"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Sterility is not adequate grounds for divorce or ........ in New Zealand. ",
      "answers": ["annulment", "nuptials", "matrimony", "marriage"],
      "correct": "annulment"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Marriage ceremonies must take place ........ 6 a.m. and 10 p.m. in a room with an open door in Manitoba. ",
      "answers": ["after", "during", "between", "from"],
      "correct": "between"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "The body of my late wife was laid to rest in a beautiful cedar ........ adorned with twelve dozen white roses. ",
      "answers": ["casket", "wreath", "grave", "morgue"],
      "correct": "casket"
    }
  ]
}
